<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Government Schemes</string>
    <string name="A">Objective of this Scheme:
•	Create scientific storage capacity with allied facilities in rural areas.
•	To meet the requirements of farmers for storing farm produce, processed farm produce and agricultural inputs.
•	Promotion of grading, standardization and quality control of agricultural produce to improve their marketability.
•	Prevent distress sale immediately after harvest by providing the facility of pledge financing and marketing credit by strengthening agricultural marketing infrastructure in the country.
</string>
    <string name="B">It is implemented with a view to promote organic farming in the country. To improve soil health and organic matter content and increase net income of the farmer so as to realise premium prices.  Under this scheme, an area of 5 lakh acre is targeted to be covered though 10,000 clusters of 50 acre each, from the year 2015-16 to 2017-18.</string>
    <string name="C">PMFBY is an actuarial premium based scheme under which farmer has to pay maximum premium of 2% for Kharif, 1.5% for Rabi food & oilseed crops and 5% for annual commercial/horticultural crops and remaining part of the actuarial/bidded premium is shared equally by the Centre and State Government.  One of the objectives of the scheme is to facilitate prompt claims settlement. The claims must be settled within two months of harvest subject to timely provision of both yield data and share of premium subsidy by the State Government. </string>
    <string name="D">Soil Health Card Scheme is a scheme launched by the Government of India in 19 February 2015.[1] Under the scheme, the government plans to issue soil cards to farmers which will carry crop-wise recommendations of nutrients and fertilisers required for the individual farms to help farmers to improve productivity through judicious use of inputs.
The scheme aims at promoting soil test based and balanced use of fertilisers to enable farmers to release higher yields at lower cost.[3] also the main objective is to aware growers about the appropriate amount of nutrients for the concerned crop depending on the quality of soil.
An amount of ₹568 crore (US$79 million) was allocated by the government for the scheme.[1] In 2016 Union budget of India, ₹100 crore (US$14 million) has been allocated to states for making soil health cards and set up labs.
The target for 2015–16 is to collect 100 lakh soil samples and test these for issue of soil health cards.[5] 2 crore cards are under printing and will be distributed before March 2016.[5] The government plans to distribute 12 crore soil cards by 2017.
</string>
    <string name="E">This scheme is initiated to regulate use of urea, enhance availability of nitrogen to the crop and reduce cost of fertilizer application.  NCU slows down the release of fertilizer and makes it available to the crop in an effective manner. The entire quantity of domestically manufactured and imported urea is now neem coated.  It reduces the cost of cultivation and improves soil health management.</string>
    <string name="F">It provides e-marketing platform at national level and support creation of infrastructure to enable e-marketing.
This innovative market process is revolutionizing agriculture markets by ensuring better price discovery. It brings in transparency and competition to enable farmers to get improved remuneration for their produce moving towards ‘One Nation One Market’. 
</string>
</resources>
